http://parentsguidecordblood.org/en/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
About Cord Blood Birth in My CountryCord Blood ValueHow Banks WorkInfographicFAQsFamily Banking Family Banks in My CountryWorld Map Family BanksHelp for families in needPublic Donation How to Donate Cord BloodUSA Donation HospitalsPublic Banks in My CountryWorld Map Public BanksTherapies Available Diseases TreatedClinical Trials Cord BloodClinical Trials Cord TissueOdds of useMilestonesCord Blood Resources Parent BrochuresDelayed Cord ClampingAccreditation StandardsUS State RegulationsAABB BanksFACT BanksNewsletter NewsContentsAbout Us About UsBoard of DirectorsAdvisory PanelStaffContactSearch formSearch
You are hereHome » Privacy Policy Privacy Policy Last Modified: 1 January, 2020This Privacy Policy explains how Parent’s Guide to Cord Blood Foundation (the “Foundation”, “we” or “us”), operator of the websites Parent’s Guide to Cord Blood at parentsguidecordblood.org and the Cord Blood Industry Report at cordbloodindustryreport.org (collectively, the “Sites”) collects and uses the information you provide to us. Please be sure to read this entire Privacy Policy before using the Sites. This Privacy Policy governs your use of the Sites.Information We CollectWhen you visit or use the Sites, we may collect the following types of information:Personal information you choose to provide to us such as your name, mailing address, professional affiliation, email address, financial information, and any medical information you willingly choose to provide to the Sites. You may provide this information, for example, when you submit questions to the Parent’s Guide to Cord Blood, or when you request a license to access the Cord Blood Industry Report.Non-personal information including, but not limited to, IP address, mobile device type and identifier, operating system, browser type, the date and time of a visit or use, the pages visited on the Sites, the time spent viewing specific pages of the Sites, and frequency of return visits to the Sites.  This information may be automatically sent to us by your web browser or device.Aggregated information as you and others browse and use the Sites.Uses of InformationWe may use the information we collect from you for purposes such as:To respond to your inquiries, questions, and requests submitted to Parent’s Guide to Cord Blood;To subscribe you to the Foundation’s Newsletter and/or other Foundation e-mail lists;To grant your request for a license to access the Cord Blood Industry Report;To process your financial payment for the Cord Blood Industry Report or your donation to the Foundation;To identify your location so that we may customize the Sites, for example, to offer cord blood education appropriate to the options available in the country where you are located;To conduct research about your use of the Sites and our services; andFor any other purpose specified at the time of collection.We will not sell the information we collect about you to any other parties.  The Foundation does share information with third party service providers, such as payment processors, in connection with the services we provide.  These service providers are required to use and safeguard your personal information in compliance with this Privacy Policy.If we or some or all of our assets are acquired by another organization, that organization will possess the information collected by us, and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your information as described in this Privacy Policy.We may disclose personal information or other data to comply with law or legal requirements, enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements, or protect our rights, property, or safety of our users, or others.SecurityWe take reasonable measures to help maintain the information we collect through our Sites in a secure manner.Links to Third Party SitesOur Sites may contain links to other websites operated by third parties we do not control and this Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected through our Sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these other websites when you visit them.Your ChoicesYou can unsubscribe from any of the Foundation’s email lists at any time by following the instructions included within any email you receive from us.Notice to California ResidentsThe California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) provides California residents with specific rights regarding their personal information.Sale of Personal InformationWe will not sell your personal information as we understand those terms to be defined by the California Consumer Privacy Act and its implementing regulations. We have not sold your personal information in the past 12 months.Non-Discrimination RightsWe will not discriminate against California residents for exercising their rights as described in this section.Your Rights With Regard to Your Personal InformationYou have the right to request access to your personal information.You have the right to request that we delete your personal information.How to request access to and deletion of your personal information If you have provided any personal information to us and wish to have it deleted, please contact us via email: info@parentsguidecordblood.org. Please allow for up to 45 days to fulfill your request.Changes to Our Privacy PolicyFrom time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy. We will notify you of any changes to our Privacy Policy by posting any updated policies on this page. We encourage you to visit this area frequently to stay informed.Contact UsIf you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@parentsguidecordblood.org.
Back to Top
